Anthony Lewis Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Annual File, 1949-2007 (Box II:1-843)
  - 1976
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights, (3 folders)
    - "H-J" miscellaneous, (6 folders) (Box II:120)
    - Kennedy family
    - Kissinger, Henry, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Law
    - Legal Action Center, New York, N.Y. (Box II:121)
    - Levi, Edward H., (6 folders)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:122)
    - Middle East
    - "M" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Nadjari, Maurice, (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:123)
    - New York, N.Y., (2 folders)
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M., (4 folders)
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity (Box II:124)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Politics
      - Brown, Jerry, (2 folders)
      - Campaign expenditure
      - Carter, Jimmy, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:125)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Humphrey, Hubert H.
      - Jackson, Henry M.
      - Shriver, Sargent
      - Transition
    - Portugal
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:126)
      - Libel and privacy, (4 folders)
      - Presidential campaign
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A.
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Soviet Union (Box II:127)
    - Speeches, (10 folders)
    - Supreme Court
    - Surroundings, (2 folders) (Box II:128)
    - "S-U" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Vietnam
    - Virgona, Hank, etchings
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Wiretapping
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1977 (Box II:129)
    - Africa
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Rhodesia
      - South Africa, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:130)
    - Amnesty
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Bell, Griffin B., (2 folders)
    - Biko, Steve, (1 folder) (Box II:131)
    - Busing
    - Bylines
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Cambodia, (2 folders)
    - Capital punishment (Box II:132)
    - Carter, Jimmy
    - Central Intelligence Agency, (3 folders)
    - Congress
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - Crime (Box II:133)
    - Criminal Code Reform Act, (2 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense and disarmament
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy, (2 folders) (Box II:134)
    - Energy, (2 folders)
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous (Box II:135)
    - Great Britain
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Trip, (3 folders)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Crimson (Box II:136)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights, (2 folders)
    - "H-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kaufman, Irving R.
    - Kissinger, Henry, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:137)
    - Lance, Bert
    - Law
    - Legal Action Center, New York, N.Y.
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Medical news
    - Middle East
    - "M" miscellaneous (Box II:138)
    - New York
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M., (3 folders)
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Pentagon Papers, correspondence
    - Press (Box II:139)
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act, (3 folders)
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Great Britain, (2 folders) (Box II:140)
      - Halkin v. Helms, (2 folders)
      - S. 1, Criminal Justice Reform Act, (2 folders)
      - United States v. Dickinson, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:141)
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Soviet Union, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:142)
    - Speeches, (4 folders)
    - Supreme Court
    - Surroundings
    - "S-U" miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box II:143)
    - Vietnam
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Watergate, (2 folders)
    - Wiretapping, (3 folders) (Box II:144)
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
  - 1978
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - General
      - Namibia, (2 folders)
      - Rhodesia (Box II:145)
      - South Africa, (5 folders)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Bell, Griffin B., (1 folder); (7 folders) (Box II:146)
    - Biko, Steve
    - Brown, Jerry (Box II:147)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Interview and sketches, (2 folders)
      - Letters
    - Bylines
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - California
      - General
      - Trip, (1 folder) (Box II:148)
    - Cambodia
    - Carter, Jimmy
      - General
      - Personnel
    - Central Intelligence Agency, (4 folders)
    - China
    - Congress, (1 folder) (Box II:149)
    - Courts, (6 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense and disarmament (Box II:150)
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Economy, (2 folders)
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Food
    - Fund for Free Expression, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Great Britain, (1 folder) (Box II:151)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - India, trip, (2 folders)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy, Edward M.
    - Kennedy, Robert F., (2 folders) (Box II:152)
    - Kissinger, Henry, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Law, (2 folders)
    - Legal Action Center, New York, N.Y.
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Middle East
      - Camp David summit
      - General, (8 folders); (1 folders) (Box II:153, Box II:154)
      - Trip, (3 folders)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Politics, (2 folders)
    - Press
      - General
      - United States v. Dickinson, (2 folders) (Box II:155)
      - United States v. Marchetti
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous
    - Regents of the University of California v. Bakke, (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:156)
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Soviet Union
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders)
      - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box II:157)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:158)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous
    - Vietnam, (2 folders)
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Whales
    - Wiretapping, (2 folders)
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
  - 1979
    - Africa
      - Namibia, (2 folders)
      - Rhodesia (Box II:159)
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Trip
      - South Africa
        - Corporations, (3 folders)
        - General, (1 folder); (9 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:160, Box II:161)
        - Trip, (7 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:162)
    - Assassinations, (2 folders)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Brown, Jerry, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:163)
    - Bureaucracy, (3 folders)
    - Bylines, (2 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - California (Box II:164)
    - Cambodia, (3 folders)
    - Carter, Jimmy
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - China
    - Civiletti, Benjamin R., and Griffin B. Bell
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - Crime (Box II:165)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense and disarmament, (4 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy
    - Energy, (3 folders)
    - "E" miscellaneous (Box II:166)
    - Ford Foundation
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Gideon's Trumpet
    - Great Britain
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass., (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:167)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass
    - Hofstra Law Review, (4 folders)
    - Human rights, (2 folders)
    - Human rights panel, United Nations Association of the United States of America, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:168)
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Iran, (2 folders)
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - "J" miscellaneous (Box II:169)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., and John F. Kennedy, (2 folders)
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - Kissinger, Henry, (4 folders)
    - Kissinger, Henry, and David Frost
    - "K" miscellaneous (Box II:170)
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Middle East
      - Esmail, Sami
      - General, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:171)
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Nadjari, Maurice, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Politics, (1 folder) (Box II:172)
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes, (2 folders)
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett Co. v. DePasquale, (2 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain
      - Halkin v. Helms (Box II:173)
      - Herbert v. Lando
      - Libel and privacy, (2 folders)
      - Newsletters
      - Pell v. Procunier and Houchins v. KQED, (2 folders)
      - Pentagon Papers, (2 folders) (Box II:174)
      - United States v. The Progressive, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:175)
      - Zucher v. Stanford Daily, (7 folders)
    - "P-R" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:176)
    - Soviet Union
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Oct., (8 folders)
      - Nov. -Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:177)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Televison
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:178)
    - Vietnam
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Wiretapping
    - "W" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Young, Andrew
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1980
    - Afghanistan, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - General
      - Namibia, (2 folders)
      - South Africa, (4 folders) (Box II:179)
      - Zimbabwe, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:180)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews
      - Bass, Jack, Unlikely Heroes: the Dramatic Story of the Judges of the Fifth Circuit Who Translated the Supreme Court's Brown Decision into a Revolution for Equality, (2 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
    - Bureaucracy
    - Bylines
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:181)
      - Lippman, Walter
      - University of Chicago Press
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Cambodia, (4 folders)
    - Cambodian Action Update (newsletter)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box II:182)
      - Democratic National Convention
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Presidential campaign
    - Central Intelligence Agency, (4 folders)
    - Civiletti, Benjamin R., (3 folders)
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y. (Box II:183)
    - Congress
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Defense and disarmament, (3 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:184)
    - Economy
    - Energy
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Food
    - Fund for Free Expression, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:185)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet, (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:186)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Hofstra Law Review
    - Human rights
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Iran, (2 folders) (Box II:187)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., (2 folders)
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - Kissinger, Henry, (3 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:188)
    - Latin America, (2 folders)
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - McGovern, George S., (2 folders)
    - Middle East
      - General, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:189)
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation (Box II:190)
    - Nixon, Richard M., (2 folders)
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Politics, (3 folders)
    - Presidential election
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Chandler v. Florida
      - Farber, Myron, (2 folders) (Box II:191)
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett v. DePasquale, (3 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain
      - Halkin v. Helms (Box II:192)
      - Libel and privacy
      - Newsletters
      - Pentagon Papers
      - Red Lion Broadcasting Co.
      - S. 1, Criminal Justice Reform Act, (2 folders)
      - Snepp v. United States, (3 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:193)
      - United States v. Marchetti
      - United States v. The Progressive
      - Zucher v. Stanford Dailey (Box II:194)
    - Project '87
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Race
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Presidential campaign, (2 folders)
      - Republican National Convention
      - Speeches
      - Staff
      - Transition, (2 folders)
    - Religion, (2 folders) (Box II:195)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Olympics
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
      - Mar.-Oct., (10 folders) (Box II:196)
      - Nov., (3 folders) (Box II:197)
    - Supreme Court
      - The Brethren
        - General, (5 folders)
        - Letters, (3 folders)
        - Reviews (Box II:198)
      - General, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings, (4 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:199)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Vance, Cyrus R.
    - Vietnam
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Westway Highway, New York, N.Y., (3 folders)
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1981
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - General (Box II:200)
      - Namibia, (2 folders)
      - Nigeria, (2 folders)
      - South Africa, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:201)
      - Trip, (4 folders)
      - Zimbabwe, (2 folders) (Box II:202)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Bylines, (4 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:203)
    - California
    - Capital punishment
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Congress
    - Courts
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:204)
    - Defense and disarmament, (2 folders)
    - Defense, nuclear weapons, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:205)
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy, (3 folders)
    - Energy (Box II:206)
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Food
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Great Britain, (2 folders)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Haig, Alexander Meigs, (4 folders) (Box II:207)
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health
    - Human rights, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:208)
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Iran
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - Korea
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:209)
    - Lane, Mark
    - Latin America
      - Argentina
      - El Salvador, (3 folders)
      - General (Box II:210)
      - Guatemala
    - Law, (2 folders)
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Middle East
      - General, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:211)
      - Trip
    - "M" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:212)
    - Poland
    - Politics
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes, (2 folders)
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett v. DePasquale
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain (Box II:213)
      - Libel and privacy, (3 folders)
      - Pentagon Papers
      - S. 1, Criminal Justice Reform Act
      - Snepp v. United States
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - Assassination attempt
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Staff (Box II:214)
    - Religion, (2 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Soviet Union, (2 folders)
    - Speeches (Box II:215)
      - Feb.-Oct., (10 folders)
      - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:216)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Timmerman, Jacobo, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:217)
    - Todd, Ruthven, (2 folders)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:218)
    - Vietnam
    - "V-Z" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
  - 1982
    - Africa
      - Ethiopia
      - General
      - Namibia, (2 folders)
      - South Africa, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:219)
      - Zimbabwe, (2 folders)
    - Anderson, John B., (3 folders)
    - Antitrust
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews
    - Bylines, (2 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:220)
    - Califano, Joseph, A., Jr.
    - California
    - Cambodia
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders)
    - Courts, (1 folder) (Box II:221)
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - Nuclear weapons, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:222)
    - Defense and disarmament
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Economy, (3 folders)
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Fund for Free Expression (Box II:223)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet
    - Great Britain
      - General
      - Trip
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Haig, Alexander Meigs
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health
    - Human rights
      - East Timor, (1 folder) (Box II:224)
      - General, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Iran
    - Ireland, (3 folders)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:225)
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - Kissinger, Henry, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Argentina, (2 folders)
      - Chile, (5 folders)
      - Cuba (Box II:226)
      - El Salvador, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Guatemala, (2 folders)
      - Nicaragua
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Middle East
      - Books, (2 folders)
      - General, (8 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:227, Box II:228)
      - Lebanon
        - General, (6 folders)
        - Sabra and Shatila Massacre, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:229)
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - New York Times
    - Nieman Foundation, (2 folders)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box II:230)
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - PEN American Center, New York, N.Y.
    - Poland, (2 folders)
    - Politics, (3 folders)
    - Press
      - Freedom of Information Act, (2 folders)
      - Gannett v. DePasquale
      - General
      - Libel and privacy, (5 folders) (Box II:231)
      - Newsletters
      - Pentagon Papers
      - The Progressive
      - Red Lion Broadcasting Co.
      - Snepp v. United States
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race, (4 folders) (Box II:232)
    - Reagan, Ronald, (3 folders)
    - Religion
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Smith, William French, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:233)
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - Speeches
      - Jan. 13-28, (4 folders)
      - Jan. 30 (Box II:234)
      - Feb.-June, (8 folders)
      - Oct. 1-14
      - Oct. 21, (1 folder) (Box II:235)
      - Oct. 28-30
      - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders)
    - Stolz, Preble, (4 folders)
    - Supreme Court, (5 folders) (Box II:236)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Television, (2 folders)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:237)
    - Vietnam
    - "V-Z" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
  - 1983
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - General
      - Mozambique, (2 folders)
      - Namibia
      - South Africa (Box II:238)
        - General, (6 folders)
        - Trip, (2 folders) (Box II:239)
      - Zimbabwe, (2 folders)
    - Andrew Silk Dissertation Fellowship
    - Aspen Institute, Aspen, Colo., (2 folders)
    - "A" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Bylines (Box II:240)
      - Columbia Law Review, (4 folders)
      - General, (3 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:241)
    - Cambodia
    - Capital punishment, (3 folders)
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Clubs
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (3 folders)
    - Courts
    - Crime (Box II:242)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - Nuclear weapons, (8 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:243)
    - Defense and disarmament
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy, (2 folders)
    - Europe, (2 folders)
    - "E" miscellaneous (Box II:244)
    - Federal Bar Council
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Fund For Free Expression
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet
    - Great Britain
      - General
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass. (Box II:245)
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (2 folders)
    - Human Rights
      - East Timor
      - General, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - India, (3 folders)
    - Ireland
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kennedy, John F., and Edward M. Kennedy, (2 folders) (Box II:246)
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - Korea, (2 folders)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Argentina
      - Chile, (2 folders)
      - Cuba (Box II:247)
      - El Salvador, (4 folders)
      - General
      - Grenada, (3 folders)
      - Guatemala, (2 folders)
      - Nicaragua, (3 folders) (Box II:248)
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Massachusetts, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Medical news
    - Middle East (Box II:249)
      - Egypt, (2 folders)
      - General, (7 folders)
      - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, (2 folders)
      - Lebanon (Box II:250)
        - General, (5 folders)
        - Sabra and Shatila Massacre
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization
      - Saudi Arabia
      - Selected columns
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:251)
    - New York
    - New York Times, (2 folders)
    - Nieman Foundation, (2 folders)
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Philippines, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:252)
    - Poland
    - Politics, (3 folders)
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett Co. v. DePasquale
      - General, (4 folders) (Box II:253)
      - Great Britain
      - Libel and privacy, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:254)
      - Pentagon Papers
      - United States v. Dickinson
      - United States v. Marchetti and Snepp v. United States, (2 folders); (10 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:255, Box II:256)
      - United States v. The Progressive, (2 folders)
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:257)
    - Reagan, Ronald, (3 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Shultz, George Pratt
    - Smith, William French, (7 folders) (Box II:258)
    - Soviet Union, (4 folders)
    - Speeches (Box II:259)
      - Feb.-May, (12 folders)
      - June-Nov., (9 folders) (Box II:260)
    - Supreme Court, (4 folders)
    - Surroundings (Box II:261)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Television, (3 folders)
    - Timerman, Jacobo
    - Trollope, Anthony
    - Turkey, (2 folders)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:262)
    - Vietnam War
      - Ghost column, (2 folders)
      - General
    - "V-Z" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
  - 1984
    - Adelman, Kenneth L.
    - Afghanistan
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - Ethiopia
      - General (Box II:263)
      - Mozambique
      - Namibia
      - South Africa, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:264)
      - Transkei, (2 folders)
      - Zimbabwe
    - Aspen, Colo.
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, (2 folders) (Box II:265)
    - Bush, George